[Music] It's
[Música]
not that they're sending me something that
No es que me están mandando una cosa que
I was thinking about man but don't do
yo la estuve pensando tío pero no me la
n't tell me or aunt daddy You're still
no me la contéis o tía papi Sigues en
live me who went to lunch we've been at it for
directo yo que me fui a almorzar
two hours and 20 I'm not going to
llevamos dos horitas y 20 ya no voy a
be much longer one more hour at
estar mucho más una horita más como
most a few more chemitas at most no Let's
mucho unos chemitas más como mucho no A
see it seems they noticed today
ver es que por lo visto han cogido hoy
that in this girl's conversations
que en las conversaciones de esta chica
and in the video she has another
y en el vídeo tiene otro nombre de
username dude [ __ ] zebra
usuario tío fucking cebra
[ __ ] unicorn
fucking unicor
Let's see what the image was
A ver vamos a ver cuál era la imagen
[Music]
[Música]
that the girl had in her profile really let's
que tenía la chica en el perfil en
see maybe she had that name
a ver a lo mejor tenía ese nombre
yes she had [ __ ] Unicorn as a name it
sí tenía fucking Unicorn de nombre
matches the profile that we said it
coincide con el perfil que hemos dicho
matches this profile look it
coincide con este perfil mira
matches this profile
coincide con este perfil
with the one that doesn't put her age [ __ ]
con el que no pone la edad fucking
Unicorn Yeah yeah Look this was the
Unicorn Sí sí Mira es que este era el
profile look at the Pikachu okay Pikachu and
perfil mira el Pikachu vale el Pikachu y
[ __ ] unicorn no it didn't put her age
fucking unicor no no ponía su edad
without more okay let's see what
sin más vale a ver qué es lo que ha
banito said
dicho banito
my answer
mi respuesta
basically I think that a person who
básicamente Pienso que una persona que
could betray a friendship without a doubt I'm
podría traicionar una amistad sin duda
not going to tell you the  why If you want to
no voy a decirte el porqué Si quieres
talk about it when I go to Barcelona we'll
hablarlo cuando vaya a Barcelona lo
talk about it in person
hablamos en persona
damn
[__]
this guy has passed by not saying
ha pasado el cabrón este de no decir
anything it sounds terrible sorry I can't do
nada se escucha fatal lo siento no puedo
anything let's see I'm going to try to
hacer nada a ver voy a intentarlo
put it better
ponerlo mejor
damn he has passed by not saying anything Let's see do
[__] ha pasado de no decir nada A ver
n't we have better quality of this
no tenemos mejor calidad de esto
basically I think they're playing
básicamente pienso que están jugando a
a game Okay and a question comes up that
un juego Vale y sale una pregunta que
says Who would be capable of betraying
dice Quién sería capaz de traicionar a
another
otro
and they're here
y están aquí
Ari cristinini I don't know who and Bye Paul I do
Ari cristinini no sé quién y Bye Paul
n't know if it's reven Juan guarnizo Carola and
no sé si es reven Juan guarnizo Carola y
karcher okay let's
karcher vale
see I think they're sending it to me
a ver que creo que me lo están mandando
with more quality
con más calidad
Yeah yeah but we don't have it with more quality
Sí ya pero no lo tenemos con más calidad
betray a friendship then Juan
traicionar una amistad entonces Juan
is saying I know the answer
está diciendo yo se la respuesta
immediately as soon as I read the
inmediatamente nada más que he leído la
question and if I think of a person who
pregunta y si pienso en una persona que
could betray a friendship without a doubt
podría traicionar una amistad sin duda
without a doubt karches I'm
sin duda alguna karches
not going to tell you why
no voy a decirte por qué
if he wants to when I go to Barcelona we'll
si quiere cuando vaya Barcelona lo
talk about it in person
hablamos en persona
That was a long time ago it's
Eso fue hace tiempo
not from now it's not
no es de ahora
not from now then
no es de ahora entonces
[ __ ] well how good How good bye because
[__] pues qué bien Qué buen bye porque
[ __ ] they have to go now they have to go
[__] que tienen que ir ahora tienen que
precisely to they have to go
ir precisamente a
precisely now to the to the
tienen que ir precisamente ahora a lo de
from the squid game in Barcelona
a lo del juego del calamar en Barcelona
is from a long time ago
es de hace mucho
the mother who gave birth to me the internet
la madre que me parió el internet
well at least tell me what click we're
bueno por lo menos decirme que click que
going to put now it
vamos a poner ahora
is current because it is supposed to have
sí es actual porque se supone que se ha
spoken about it I will find it I will
pronunciado
where is it I will do it
lo haré dónde está
I want to feel your body I will do it here
quiero sentir tu cuerpo lo haré aquí
okay or so karches auron apparently
vale o sea karches auron al parecer por
told carcha in private that he has no
privado le dijo a carcha que no tiene
problem with him and carche came back
ningún problema con él y carche volvió
very cool saying that they
muy chulo diciendo que lo
misinterpreted him what he wanted to say is
malinterpretaron lo que quería decir es
that his disassociation from the
que su desvinculación de los juegos del
squid games supposedly had nothing to
calamar supuestamente no tenía nada que
do with the auron case and Beijing and
ver con la funda de auron y Beijing y
that despite the fact that there are people who
que a pesar de que hay gente que se
should apologize He doesn't expect an apology from
debería disculpar No espera disculpas de
anyone auron saved his career on the
nadie auron le salvó su carrera en
internet and came back very cool I'm
internet y volvió muy chulo yo
going to hear the words I've already
vamos a escuchar las palabras yo ya las
heard them Okay and I tell you okay
he escuchado Vale y os digo ya vale
before listening to it
antes de escucharla
I hope
espero
that auron
que auron
if it's true that he has spoken with him and
si es verdad que ha hablado con él y le
told him this
ha dicho esto
I hope he did it simply to
Espero que lo haya hecho simplemente por
be calm right now and not to
estar tranquilo ahora mismo y por no
have any [ __ ] now
tener mamoneo ahora
Because if he is going to continue with him as if
Porque si va a seguir con el como si
nothing happened
nada
I would find it a little disappointing
me parecería un poquito decepcionante
okay or so
vale o sea
honestly if from behind Oh nothing's wrong no I don't
sinceramente si por detrás Ay no pasa
want to think that I've told him
quiero pensar que se lo he dicho
so to
como para
be calm now while he
estar tranquilo ahora mientras que
finishes recovering whatever it is you know
termina de recuperarse lo que sea sabes
and not having an amoneo now no but
y no tener ahora un amoneo no pero
man whoever hasn't seen it whoever hasn't
hombre el que no lo haya visto el que no
seen Karches's true colors is
le haya visto el plumero a karches es
because he didn't want to see it okay
que no se la ha querido ver vale
mind and you've stopped getting carried away
mente y os habéis dejado de llevar mucho
by hate and I'm telling this to the whole [ __ ]
por el odio y se lo digo a todo el [__]
world who has called me Rata and I'm
mundo que me ha llamado Rata y
going to tell you do you know why
os voy a decir sabes por qué
because I've spoken to Auron
porque yo he hablado con auron por
privately and there's no problem with him
privado y no hay ningún problema con él
nor has he taken anything I've
ni se lo ha tomado mal nada de lo que he
said badly because there's nothing to take
dicho porque no hay nada que tomárselo
badly about what I've said
mal de lo que yo he dicho
that there's nothing to take badly about what
que no hay nada que tomárselo mal de lo
you've said
que tú has dicho
literally you said that you didn't want to
literalmente dijiste que no querías
comment on the delicate subject
opinar sobre el tema delicado
but let's go apart it's that it's very
pero vamos que aparte es que eso está
engraved And that's how it is
grabadísimo Y eso es así
Javi a little phrase to your friends
Javi una pequeña frase a tus amigos
close but your enemies to the good side
cerca pero tus enemigos al lado bueno
one thing is Let's see no no I do
una cosa es A ver no no yo a mis enemigo
n't have my enemies by my side
no lo tengo al lado
no one thing that one
no una cosa que a uno
cool down And then say when it arrives
se enfríe Y luego diga cuando llegue
Well then, don't bring Leo in, come on, each
Bueno pues no me metes a Leo venga cada
one goes their own way and I'll slowly ignore him
uno por su lado y voy pasando de él poco
but if I see that he keeps
a poco pero si yo veo que lo sigue
inviting him to things and such
invitando a cosas y demás
his gestures reveal that he's lying no no let's
sus gestos delatan que miente no no a
see the clip it was the one that was, I mean the clip
ver el clip fue el que fue o sea el clip
of him was saying that he didn't want to comment
de él fue diciendo que no quería opinar
on such a delicate subject referring to
de un tema tan delicado refiriéndose a
the case with the minor and that he
la funda con la menor y que eso no
wasn't, he didn't feel capable of
estaba no se sentía en la capacidad de
commenting on that subject but if
opinar sobre ese tema pero que si la
things continued like this he would disassociate himself from the
cosa seguía así se desvinculaba de los
squid games I
juegos del calamar
mean the clip was very clear
o sea el clip fue muy claro
like he already distrusted auron and saying
como desconfiando ya de auron y diciendo
if this isn't clarified I'm disassociating myself
como esto no se aclare yo me desvinculo
from here
de aquí
Now I'm not going to ask or demand that
Ahora yo no voy a pedir ni exigir que me
people apologize to me for that there are people
dé la gente disculpas de eso hay gente
who called me Rat and all that because I don't
que me llamó Rata y todo eso porque no
want apologies from those people it's
quiero las disculpas de esa gente
not worth it The only thing I can
no merece la pena Yo lo único que puedo
say is to all the people who weren't
decir es a toda la gente que no estaba
attending these days
cursando estos días
how badly he was harassing you
qué mal estaba acosando
have the girlfriend who deserves you to be a carcha
tienes la novia que te merece carcha
without more
sin más
for being disloyal or a false friend when
por desleal o falso amigo cuando
literally I  I have spoken with Auron
literalmente yo he hablado con auron por
privately and there is no problem
privado y no hay ningún problema
between him and I We are still the
Entre él y yo
same The
Seguimos igual
only thing I can tell you is that
lo único que os puedo decir es que
on top of giving veracity to a thread that
encima dándole veracidad a un hilo que
put everything here on its own weight
ponía todo acá por su propio peso
what he said was what he said and if now he
lo que dijo fue lo que dijo y si ahora
is denying it because he is collecting
lo está negando porque está recogiendo
cable because everyone has seen
cable porque todo el mundo lo ha visto
the mask
la careta
what he said was what he said if you
lo que dijo fue lo que dijo si me
stopped following me because you followed me do not
dejaste de seguir porque me seguías no
follow me anymore I do not want you around here
me sigas nunca más no te quiero por aquí
no no he is no longer serious
no no tiene más en serio
now you have been left like clowns
ahora habéis quedado como payasos
you have been left like a clown man for
habéis quedado como payaso hombre para
me honestly the one who would look bad
mí sinceramente el que quedaría mal
for me I do not know what you think one
para mí no sé qué pensáis ustedes un
second I have to look at something
segundo que tengo que mirar una cosa
for me the one who would look bad if we see
para mí el que quedaría mal si vemos a
that guy in series next to Auron
ese chico en series al lado de auron
giving him more fame and more gifts for me the one who would
dándole más fama y más regalito para mí
look bad would be Auron I
el que quedaría mal sería auron
say it clearly okay or I mean
lo digo claramente vale o sea
and this is live
y esto está en directo
This is live at the moment in
Esto está en directo en el momento en el
which now one moment
que ahora un momento
the moment in which Auron puts that
el momento en el que auron pone esa
story that he
historia de
then deletes instantly this is at the
que luego borra al instante es en el
moment in which we are here
momento en el que estamos aquí en
live breaking everything down  the karches thing
directo desmenuzando todo lo de karches
this is live you can check it out
esto está en directo lo podéis comprobar
we are here live reacting to
estamos aquí en directo reaccionando
everything the carch thing says done what
todo lo del carché dice hecho lo que
cache said was very clear I mean it's not that it
dijo cache fue muy clarito O sea no es
was brief that it could be
que fuera escueto que se pueda
misinterpreted no
malinterpretar no
what karcher said was very clear I
lo que dijo karcher fue muy clarito yo
can't comment on this issue it's
de este tema no me puedo pronunciar es
a very delicate issue I don't feel I have the
un tema muy delicado no me siento con la
capacity to comment but if
capacidad de pronunciarme pero si las
things continue as they are I'm disassociating myself
cosas siguen como están yo me desvinculó
from the squid game There
del juego del calamar
's no other valid explanation
No hay ninguna otra explicación válida
for why you were
por la que tú te estuvieras
disassociating yourself from the squid game it
desvinculando el juego del calamar me
surprises me a lot that the reason why
extraña mucho que el motivo por el que
you want to disassociate yourself from the
tú te quieras desvincular el juego del
squid game was because they left me and
calamar era porque me han dejado a mí y
Ricky Eddy out Okay I get the
a Ricky Eddy fuera Vale me da la
feeling it was because I was
sensación de que era porque le estaba
giving credibility to the funa
dando credibilidad a la funa
but it's not that you were giving
pero no es que le estuvieras dando
credibility to the funa it's just that your girlfriend
credibilidad a la funa es que tu novia
just came out right now a while ago we
acaba de salir ahora mismo hace un rato
saw her saying that well the
que la hemos visto diciendo que bueno
thing about age in the the age in
que lo de la edad en la lo de la edad en
life hasn't been very proven it can't be
la vida no ha quedado muy demostrado no
accredited no something like that she said
se puede acreditar no algo así ha dicho
no no
no no
for me  I say it clearly here publicly
para mí lo digo claro aquí públicamente
and I'm going to say it until the end eh I
y lo voy a decir hasta el final eh
trust Auron because I hope that what
Confío en auron pues espero que esto que
the guy is saying is not
está diciendo el chico no sea así esté
distorted eh For me like this guy He's
tergiversado eh Para mí como este chico
still there in the group and the whole
Sigue estando ahí en el grupito y todo
thing for
el rollo
me the one who looks really bad with
para mí el que queda muy mal con todo el
everyone is Auron I don't give a
mundo es auron a mí me la trae el alma
damn I mean I'm nobody in
floja o sea yo no soy nadie en la vida
anyone's life but man
de nadie pero hombre
[Music] you
[Música]
have let yourselves be carried away by the hate
os habéis dejado llevar por el odio
that a person has tried to put in your heads a
que os ha intentado meter en la cabeza
person towards me when
una persona una persona hacia mí cuando
literally what I said is the most
literalmente yo lo que dije es lo más
normal thing in the world
normal del mundo
the most normal thing in the world
lo más normal del mundo
the most normal thing in the world man
lo más normal del mundo tío
the most normal thing in the world is that you
lo más normal del mundo es que tú te
inform yourself before making statements
informe antes de hacer unas afirmaciones
like that having Auron's followers
como esa teniendo Los Seguidores de
if your followers were yours like
si tus seguidores fueran tuyo como los
mine Well you still know but your
míos Pues todavía tú sabes pero tus
followers are all Auron's all
seguidores son todos los de auron todo
Auron's not the euros they are not all
lo de auron no los de euros no son todos
your followers but yours
los seguidores tuyos pero los tuyos sí
are all Auron's
son todos de auron
So the most normal thing
Entonces lo más normal
is to inform yourself like I did I already knew
es informarte como hice yo yo ya sabía
before the subject that the  about age, about the
antes del tema que la lo de la edad lo
profile, about everything, I was it
del perfil lo de todo yo yo lo fui
Knowing
Sabiendo
and you having contact with the direct one
y tú teniendo un contacto con el directo
that you say that if things continue How they are, it
que tú digas que si la cosa sigue Cómo
disassociates you from the squid games
está te desvincula de los juegos del
at the moment in which you said it how
en el momento en el que lo dijiste cómo
things were at the moment you
estaba la cosa en el momento que lo
said it,
dijiste
everyone thought what they wanted to think
cada uno pensaba lo que quería pensar
And if things continue like this, you meant that it
Y si sigue la cosa así te referías a que
was credible,
era creíble
the one who smells this
al que le huele esto
only showed his nature no no, the one who
solo mostró su naturaleza no no al que
buys this, there's no way to
le cuele esto no
take it and that's it and that's it,
hay por dónde cogerlo
so well, you guys
y ya está y es lo que hay así que bueno
looked a little like clowns and that's it,
quedasteis un poquito como payasos y ya
no more has been
está no tiene más
said, this what was said, I don't want an
dicho esto lo dicho no quiero ni
apology from anyone or anything like that, okay, well, I don't
disculpas de nadie ni nada de eso vale
want them No, they're not worth it to me
bueno no las quiero No no me merecen la
but just so you know that, no
pena pero que sepáis eso
one's apology, I would send an egg for someone to
Disculpa de nadie mandaría un huevo que
apologize to you, someone with you on top of you would
te disculpara alguien contigo encima
send an egg let's
mandaría huevo
see what people think, would
a ver qué piensa la gente
people say,
dice la gente los nervios de
Noni's nerves are an example, she said that she was bad
noni es un ejemplo dijo que estaba mal
about Auron and she doesn't feel well to give her
por lo de auron y no se siente bien para
opinion on anything
opinar de nada
when you have contact with the
cuando tienes contacto con el
protagonist that the protagonist has  He
protagonista que el protagonista ha
picked up the phone every single day because
cogió el teléfono todos estos días pues
I was in contact with him almost every
yo estaba en contacto con él casi todos
day
los días
So if you wanted to know you could
O sea que si quería saber podías
ask So it's
preguntar
not like someone is going to
O sea que no es decir que a uno va a
drop the phone, they have
soltar el teléfono
n't dropped it any day, is it
que no lo ha soltado ningún día
okay
vale
for you to pick up your Stream with
para que tú cojas en tu Stream con Los
Auron's Followers and say if this
Seguidores de auron y digas si esto
continues as it is now I'm disassociating myself from the
sigue como está ahora me desvinculo del
Squid Game
juego del calamar
no no no no no
no no no no no
No if your friend is telling you that he
No si a ti tu amigo te está diciendo que
's innocent you go to the Squid Games
es inocente tú vas a los juegos del
and if the brands leave you go to the
y si se van las marcas tú vas a los
Squid Games
juegos del calamar
because you have to be there in the good times and in the
porque hay que estar las buenas y en las
bad times
malas
not just the good times but this ghost
no solo las buenas pero este fantasma
thinks that someone wants to apologize
piensa que alguien quiere disculparse
for how false he was with Auron if he's made
por lo falso que fue con auron si ha
worse by revealing that he spoke to him
quedado peor revelando que hablo con el
to ask him if everything was okay no
para preguntarle si estaba todo bien
no but let's see it's not like he's
no no pero vamos a ver no es que haya
made worse by asking him that I do
quedado peor preguntándole que eso ya me
n't care what I want to think
trae sin cuidado lo que yo quiero pensar
is that Auron
es que auron
has done this
ha hecho esto
[Music]
[Música]
to
para
avoid problems and finish
no tener problemas y terminarse de
recovering and he has said Yes yes whatever
recuperar y le ha dicho Sí sí vale lo
you say but that you pick up and that  you're
que tú digas pero que tú cojas y que
going to be so normal, things here would
vayas a estar tan normal la cosa aquí me
seem very strange to me, eh. Honestly, I
resultarían muy raro eh De verdad yo no
wasn't one to repeat to anyone a thousand times that it
fue uno a nadie repetir mil veces que me
seemed wrong to harass anyone. I spoke of
parecía mal acosar a nadie hablé de
both positions and I tried to also
ambas posturas e intenté que también
speak well of Auron and despite the fact that he is not Auron's friend, it was Marius Optimas who misinterpreted it. But in the end it's my point of view, I also want to share it, people change, I want to keep thinking about it. I don't know if I'm innocent, if I'm stupid, if I'm someone who is putting blinders on,
alguien que se está poniendo vendas en
but I think that people change. being
los ojos pero creo que la gente cambia
20 years old, being 24 years old, being 22
tener 20 años tener 24 años tener 22
years old is having a certain age,
años es tener una edad
but it's true that I think that at
pero sí que es cierto que creo que a los
10 years old
10 años
you can look back and feel [ __ ] disgusted and
puedes ver para atrás y darte [__] asco
think that that is something that you would
y pensar que eso es algo que no harías
never do again in your [ __ ] life. I think that everyone makes mistakes to a greater or lesser extent, but the ones I'm going to keep thinking about and I want to think that people change. And that doesn't mean that
Y eso no quita que no se le tenga que
what you've done in your past shouldn't be given weight
dar peso a lo que has hecho en tu pasado
and that people should know it and
y que la gente lo tenga que saber y
have the right to know it.
tenga su derecho a saberlo
girl but you know it's not supposed to be in this
niña pero sabes Se supone que en este
tweet that he's
tweet
founding auron
no está fundando a auron
but it's supposed to be in this tweet that he's not
pero se supone que en este tuit no está
working at all I mean if you just
funcionando en nada O sea si acabas de
said that you trust in change but that you
decir que confías en el cambio pero que
have to know what's in
hay que saber lo que hay en el grupo de
Aura's group in the Craft ring and then he was
Aura en el ring Craft y luego fue
invited to tortilla
invitado en tortilla
Oh sorry son I didn't hear you I
Ay Perdona hijo no te he escuchado Yo
hope auron takes into account everything I
espero que auron lo tome en cuenta todo
mentioned to carch maybe now
lo que menciono a carché quizás ahora no
is not the time we'll see if carchez will be
es el momento veremos si carchez estará
in tortillaland 3 auron is perfectly
en tortillaland 3 auron es perfectamente
aware of karcher if the
consciente de lo de karcher si las
chairs that I have to put screws on
sillas que le tengo que poner tornillos
and I'll put it on him once and for all auron is
y se lo pongo de una [__] vez auron es
perfectly aware of
perfectamente consciente de lo de
karcher
karcher
if he told him that I
si le ha dicho eso
hope it's to
espero que sea
not have a move and
Por no tener movida y
recover calmly and then when he
recuperarse tranquilo y luego cuando
returns he will
vuelva
take measures or take measures or
tomará medidas o tomará medidas o
act in another way with him maybe it does
actuará de otra manera con él a lo mejor
n't mean that he will fight with him or
no quiere decir que se pelee con él o
sink him or whatever it is that I think the
que lo hunda o lo que sea que yo creo
logical thing would be a review in a
que lo lógico sería un repasito en un
video
videito
But what I believe here is that it
Pero lo que yo creo aquí es que
will have been to calm down because well the
habrá sido para calmar porque bueno el
tweet that she just posted but
tweet que acaba de poner ella pero
girls if you're saying
chicas si estás diciendo
that you think people change but that
qué crees que la gente cambia pero que
if the past is [ __ ] disgusting that
si el pasado da [__] asco que todo el
everyone has to know it and it has to be
mundo lo tiene que saber y hay que
exposed And that doesn't mean that we shouldn't
exponerlo Y eso no quita que no se le
give weight to what you've done in
tenga que dar peso a lo que has hecho en
your past and that people have to
tu pasado y que la gente lo tenga que
know it and that people have to know it
saber y que la gente lo tiene que saber
And apart from that, let's
Y aparte aparte
see if I know how to write it Oh well it's right
a ver si sé escribirlo Ah bueno está
here next door
aquí al lado
yes my parents started at 40 50 not 14
sí mis padres empezaron con 40 50 no 14
24 and 1930 okay messing with Auro and
24 y 1930 vale metiéndose con Auro y
me he
conmigo
doesn't understand that both people are in
no entiende que ambas personas están en
different stages of life and that the
etapas diferentes de la vida y que la
older one will be able to take advantage of it and
mayor podrá tomar ventaja sobre ello y
do whatever she wants with the younger
hacer lo que quiera con el menor
tremendous
tremendo
come on you tell me
vamos que tú me digas a mí
that Auron this is going to happen let's
que auron esto lo va a pasar
see the people who are saying it say
a ver la gente que está diciendo dice
the nerves of not being able to stop eating
los nervios de no poder parar de comer
There is the one who doesn't owe it doesn't fear it and the one
Hay el que no la debe no la tema y el
who has a clear conscience doesn't
que tiene su conciencia limpia no se
get so nervous
pone tan nerviosito
I would also tell my friend that
yo también le diría a mi amigo que no
nothing's wrong
pasa nada
Auron it's like that I don't know what happened and
auron es así no sé qué habrá pasado y
how they might have talked
cómo habrán hablado
little thing  Linda thought that we wanted to
cosita linda pensó que le queríamos
apologize and she acts like I don't want them anymore.
pedir disculpas y se hace el ya no las
I didn't hate you but I didn't come across
yo no te tiré odio pero tampoco quede
as a clown either. I still maintain my position.
como payasa sigo manteniendo mi posición
Whoever doesn't maintain their position doesn't
el que no mantenga su posición es que no
want to be disappointed with Karcher. In other
quiere desengañarse con karcher
words, whoever doesn't maintain assumptions, they do
o sea el que no mantenga suposiciones
n't want to be disappointed with Karches.
que no quieren desengañarse con karches
Without further ado, Karch's position is even
sin más a la postura de karch es hasta
very clear. The tradition has been very
muy clara la tradición ha estado muy
clear. His
clara
mask has completely fallen off. The one
se le ha caído completamente la careta
who would look bad wouldn't be the people. The one
el que quedaría mal no sería la gente el
who would look bad would be Auron. But anyway,
que quedaría mal sería auron como Pero
each one to himself.
bueno ya cada uno haya cada uno
The salt would be very tender. I am very tender. I am very tender. I am very tender. I
la sal sería muy tierno soy muy tierno
am very tender.
tierno soy muy tierno
You know about laws.
tú sabes de leyes
[Music]
[Música]